Guide to the Vassar College Dean of Studies Records, 1867-2016
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Student Records, 1867-2016; (920 boxes) [RESTRICTED]
  - Series I. General Records, 1876-2012
    - Regular, Smith, P-Wei, 1987 (Box 461)
    - Regular, Weis-Zol, 1987 (Box 462)
    - Withdrawn, B-John, 1987 (Box 462)
    - Withdrawn, Kan-Zor, 1987 (Box 432)
    - Regular, A-Bru, 1988 (Box 469)
    - Regular, Bro-Doy, 1988 (Box 470)
    - Regular, Dro-Green, 1988 (Box 430)
    - Regular, Kan-Lev, 1988 (Box 439)
    - Regular, Levy-Mit, 1988 (Box 440)
    - Regular, Mitt-Pes, 1988 (Box 447)
    - Regular, Pic-Sch, 1988 (Box 448)
    - Regular, Sco-Tie, 1988 (Box 455)
    - Regular, Til-Zuc, 1988 (Box 456)
    - Withdrawn, Bal-Lin, 1988 (Box 463)
    - Withdrawn, Lom-Zis, 1988 (Box 464)
    - Regular, A-By, 1989 (Box 397)
    - Regular, C-Ea, 1989 (Box 423)
    - Regular, Ech-Gott, 1989 (Box 424)
    - Regular, Gou-Jam, 1989 (Box 425)
    - Regular, Jan-Lit, 1989 (Box 433)
    - Regular, Liu-Nic, 1989 (Box 434)
    - Regular, Nis-Ror, 1989 (Box 441)
    - Regular, Ros-Ste, 1989 (Box 442)
    - Regular, Ste-Wei, 1989 (Box 449)
    - Regular, Weinman-Zuk, 1989 (Box 450)
    - Withdrawn, Adl-Hal, 1989 (Box 450)
    - Withdrawn, Hir-Zis, 1989 (Box 457)
    - Regular, A-Cas, 1990 (Box 458)
    - Regular, Cau-Fra, 1990 (Box 465)
    - Regular, Fran-Harr, 1990 (Box 466)
    - Regular, Har-Koz, 1990 (Box 471)
    - Regular, Kra-Mey, 1990 (Box 472)
    - Regular, Mey-Rac, 1990 (Box 477)
    - Regular, Rap-Shi, 1990 (Box 478)
    - Regular, Sho-Wec, 1990 (Box 485)
    - Regular, Wei-Zod, 1990 (Box 486)
    - Withdrawn, A-Nel, 1990 (Box 493)
    - Withdrawn, Nev-Z, 1990 (Box 494)
    - Regular, Aa-Bh, 1991 (Box 497)
    - Regular, Bi-Cog, 1991 (Box 498)
    - Regular, Coh-Eim, 1991 (Box 501)
    - Regular, Ein-Gur, 1991 (Box 502)
    - Regular, Gus-Joi, 1991 (Box 473)
    - Regular, Jon-Lit, 1991 (Box 474)
    - Regular, Lon-Mog, 1991 (Box 479)
    - Regular, Moh-Pus, 1991 (Box 480)
    - Regular, Rah-Sil, 1991 (Box 487)
    - Regular, Sim-Tul, 1991 (Box 488)
    - Regular, Tun-Won, 1991 (Box 495)
    - Regular, Woo-Z, 1991 (Box 496)
    - Withdrawn, A-Gom, 1991 (Box 496)
    - Withdrawn, Hal-Z, 1991 (Box 499)
    - Regular, Adu-Bri, 1992 (Box 500)
    - Regular, Broad-Day, 1992 (Box 516)
    - Regular, Deg-For, 1992 (Box 517)
    - Regular, Fra-Guz, 1992 (Box 475)
    - Regular, Hab-Ive, 1992 (Box 476)
    - Regular, Jac-Kur, 1992 (Box 481)
    - Regular, Lab-Maz, 1992 (Box 482)
    - Regular, McC-Nur, 1992 (Box 489)
    - Regular, O'br-Rey, 1992 (Box 490)
    - Regular, Rich-Sen, 1992 (Box 518)
    - Regular, Sha-Swa, 1992 (Box 483)
    - Regular, Tan-Wes, 1992 (Box 484)
    - Regular, Whi-Zym, 1992 (Box 491)
    - Withdrawn, A-Law, 1992 (Box 491)
    - Withdrawn, Lev-Zur, 1992 (Box 492)
    - Regular, A-Br, 1993 (Box 503)
    - Regular, Bu-Cr, 1993 (Box 504)
    - Regular, Da-Ey, 1993 (Box 505)
    - Regular, Fa-Go, 1993 (Box 506)
    - Regular, Gr-In, 1993 (Box 507)
    - Regular, Ja-Ku, 1993 (Box 508)
    - Regular, La-Ma, 1993 (Box 509)
    - Regular, Mc-No, 1993 (Box 510)
    - Regular, Nu-Ri, 1993 (Box 511)
    - Regular, Ro-Sp, 1993 (Box 512)
    - Regular, St-Wu, 1993 (Box 513)
    - Regular, Yo-Z, 1993 (Box 514)
    - Withdrawn, A-Gla, 1993 (Box 514)
    - Withdrawn, Gra-Z, 1993 (Box 515)
    - Regular, A-Car, 1994 (Box 638)
    - Regular, Cas-Em, 1994 (Box 639)
    - Regular, En-Go, 1994 (Box 640)
    - Regular, Gra-Je, 1994 (Box 641)
    - Regular, Jo-Le, 1994 (Box 642)
    - Regular, Li-Mo, 1994 (Box 643)
    - Regular, Mu-Pr, 1994 (Box 644)
    - Regular, O-Si, 1994 (Box 645)
    - Regular, Sm-Vo, 1994 (Box 646)
    - Withdrawn, A-Ca, 1994 (Box 647)
    - Withdrawn, Ch-M, 1994 (Box 648)
    - Withdrawn, N-Z, 1994 (Box 649)
    - Regular, A-Bub, 1995 (Box 691)
    - Regular, Buz-Dor, 1995 (Box 692)
    - Regular, Dos-Geo, 1995 (Box 693)
    - Regular, Gia-Hoo, 1995 (Box 694)
    - Regular, Hor-Land, 1995 (Box 695)
    - Regular, Lang-Mcd, 1995 (Box 696)
    - Regular, Mcg-Par, 1995 (Box 697)
    - Regular, Pat-Roy, 1995 (Box 698)
    - Regular, Rub-Ski, 1995 (Box 699)
    - Regular, Ski-Vas, 1995 (Box 700)
    - Regular, Vio-Z, 1995 (Box 701)
    - Withdrawn, A-Baum, 1995 (Box 701)
    - Withdrawn, Ben-Lee, 1995 (Box 702)
    - Withdrawn, Lew-Z, 1995 (Box 703)
    - Regular, A-Boge, 1996 (Box 709)
    - Regular, Bogu-Coo, 1996 (Box 710)
    - Regular, Cos-Few, 1996 (Box 711)
    - Regular, Fie-Hanl, 1996 (Box 712)
    - Regular, Hans-Kon, 1996 (Box 713)
    - Regular, Kor-Ma, 1996 (Box 714)
    - Regular, Mcd-Nus, 1996 (Box 715)
    - Regular, Og-Sag, 1996 (Box 716)
    - Regular, Sal-Tai, 1996 (Box 717)
    - Regular, Tak-Wil, 1996 (Box 718)
    - Withdrawn, A-Le, 1996 (Box 757)
    - Withdrawn, Lo-Th, 1996 (Box 758)
    - Withdrawn, Rob-Z, 1996 (Box 759)
    - Regular, A-Bu, 1997 (Box 723)
    - Regular, C-Dol, 1997 (Box 724)
    - Regular, Don-Gio, 1997 (Box 725)
    - Regular, Git-Hy, 1997 (Box 726)
    - Regular, I-Lef, 1997 (Box 727)
    - Regular, Leh-Mu, 1997 (Box 728)
    - Regular, N-Rin, 1997 (Box 729)
    - Regular, Rob-Sim, 1997 (Box 730)
    - Regular, Sla-Vy, 1997 (Box 731)
    - Regular, Wa-Z, 1997 (Box 736)
    - Withdrawn, A-Har, 1997 (Box 759)
    - Withdrawn, He-Tu, 1997 (Box 760)
    - Withdrawn, Ud-Z, 1997 (Box 761)
    - Regular, A-Bla, 1998 (Box 737)
    - Regular, Bod-Cor, 1998 (Box 738)
    - Regular, Cos-Fra, 1998 (Box 739)
    - Regular, Fre-Ha, 1998 (Box 740)
    - Regular, He-La, 1998 (Box 741)
    - Regular, Le-Me, 1998 (Box 742)
    - Regular, Mi-Pl, 1998 (Box 743)
    - Regular, Po-Scl, 1998 (Box 744)
    - Regular, Soc-V, 1998 (Box 745)
    - Regular, Wa-Z, 1998 (Box 746)
    - Withdrawn, A-Kol, 1998 (Box 761)
    - Withdrawn, Le-Z, 1998 (Box 790)
    - Regular, A-Br, 1999 (Box 747)
    - Regular, Bu-Del, 1999 (Box 748)
    - Regular, Den-Ge, 1999 (Box 749)
    - Regular, Gi-How, 1999 (Box 750)
    - Regular, Hoy-Lehm, 1999 (Box 751)
    - Regular, Lehr-Mo, 1999 (Box 752)
    - Regular, Mor-Py, 1999 (Box 753)
    - Regular, Qu-Smith, E, 1999 (Box 754)
    - Regular, Smith, L-Wa, 1999 (Box 755)
    - Regular, Web-Z, 1999 (Box 756)
    - Withdrawn, A-Be, 1999 (Box 790)
    - Withdrawn, Bi-Pu, 1999 (Box 791)
    - Withdrawn, Re-Z, 1999 (Box 792)
    - Regular, A-Bo, 2000 (Box 765)
    - Regular, Br-Cor, 2000 (Box 766)
    - Regular, Cos-Fl, 2000 (Box 767)
    - Regular, For-Hop, 2000 (Box 768)
    - Regular, Hor-K, 2000 (Box 769)
    - Regular, L-Mi, 2000 (Box 770)
    - Regular, Mo-Re, 2000 (Box 771)
    - Regular, Rh-Si, 2000 (Box 772)
    - Regular, Sk-V, 2000 (Box 773)
    - Regular, W-Z, 2000 (Box 774)
    - Withdrawn, A-H, 2000 (Box 792)
    - Withdrawn, I-Z, 2000 (Box 793)
    - Regular, A-Bo, 2001 (Box 779)
    - Regular, Br-Di, 2001 (Box 780)
    - Regular, Do-Gl, 2001 (Box 781)
    - Regular, Go-Hy, 2001 (Box 782)
    - Regular, I-Ky, 2001 (Box 783)
    - Regular, L-Ma, 2001 (Box 784)
    - Regular, Mc-Ow, 2001 (Box 785)
    - Regular, P-Ron, 2001 (Box 786)
    - Regular, Rop-Si, 2001 (Box 787)
    - Regular, Sk-Tu, 2001 (Box 788)
    - Regular, U-Z, 2001 (Box 789)
    - Withdrawn, A-Sh, 2001 (Box 794)
    - Withdrawn, Si-Z, 2001 (Box 805)
    - Regular, A-Bu, 2002 (Box 795)
    - Regular, Ca-Del, 2002 (Box 796)
    - Regular, Den-Gl, 2002 (Box 797)
    - Regular, Gol-Iwa, 2002 (Box 798)
    - Regular, Jag-Laz, 2002 (Box 799)
    - Regular, Le-Mil, 2002 (Box 800)
    - Regular, Min-Put, 2002 (Box 801)
    - Regular, Rag-Sch, 2002 (Box 802)
    - Regular, Se-Tow, 2002 (Box 803)
    - Regular, Tra-Zuc, 2002 (Box 804)
    - Withdrawn, A-Du, 2002 (Box 805)
    - Withdrawn, Fa-Z, 2002 (Box 806)
    - Regular, A-Boy, 2003 (Box 811)
    - Regular, Br-Cu, 2003 (Box 812)
    - Regular, D-Fl, 2003 (Box 813)
    - Regular, Fo-Ham, 2003 (Box 814)
    - Regular, Han-Joy, 2003 (Box 815)
    - Regular, Ka-Lu, 2003 (Box 816)
    - Regular, Ma-New, 2003 (Box 817)
    - Regular, Nig-Rog, 2003 (Box 818)
    - Regular, Ros-Sko, 2003 (Box 819)
    - Regular, Sl-Von, 2003 (Box 820)
    - Regular, Wa-Z, 2003 (Box 821)
    - Withdrawn, A-Ham, 2003 (Box 821)
    - Withdrawn, Han-Z, 2003 (Box 822)
    - Regular, A-Bir, 2004 (Box 827)
    - Regular, Bla-Cole, 2004 (Box 828)
    - Regular, Coll-Fag, 2004 (Box 829)
    - Regular, Fai-Gos, 2004 (Box 830)
    - Regular, Gra-Isl, 2004 (Box 831)
    - Regular, Jac-Lei, 2004 (Box 832)
    - Regular, Let-Moy, 2004 (Box 833)
    - Regular, Mro-Res, 2004 (Box 834)
    - Regular, Rev-Sol, 2004 (Box 835)
    - Regular, Sol-Wat, 2004 (Box 836)
    - Regular, Wat-Z, 2004 (Box 837)
    - Withdrawn, A-Hel, 2004 (Box 837)
    - Withdrawn, Hil-Y, 2004 (Box 838)
    - Regular, A-Bug, 2005 (Box 839)
    - Regular, Bur-Daw, 2005 (Box 840)
    - Regular, Dev-Fis, 2005 (Box 841)
    - Regular, Fla-Har, 2005 (Box 842)
    - Regular, Has-Kas, 2005 (Box 843)
    - Regular, Kat-Lin, 2005 (Box 844)
    - Regular, Lis-Mos, 2005 (Box 845)
    - Regular, Mur-Ran, 2005 (Box 846)
    - Regular, Rau-Shu, 2005 (Box 847)
    - Regular, Sil-Uy, 2005 (Box 848)
    - Regular, Vac-Zip, 2005 (Box 849)
    - Withdrawn, A-Z, 2005 (Box 850)
    - Regular, A-Bru, 2006 (Box 851)
    - Regular, Buc-Dem, 2006 (Box 852)
    - Regular, Den-Fuk, 2006 (Box 853)
    - Regular, Gaf-Huf, 2006 (Box 854)
    - Regular, Hum-Law, 2006 (Box 855)
    - Regular, Lee-Men, 2006 (Box 856)
    - Regular, Mer-Per, 2006 (Box 857)
    - Regular, Pet-Sax, 2006 (Box 858)
    - Regular, Sch-Var, 2006 (Box 859)
    - Regular, Vel-Zwa, 2006 (Box 860)
    - Withdrawn, A-Z, 2006 (Box 861)
    - Regular, A-Bra, 2007 (Box 863)
    - Regular, Bro-Coo, 2007 (Box 864)
    - Regular, Cor-Fre, 2007 (Box 865)
    - Regular, Fri-Hi, 2007 (Box 866)
    - Regular, Ho-Kre, 2007 (Box 867)
    - Regular, Ku-Mcc, 2007 (Box 868)
    - Regular, Mcd-Pet, 2007 (Box 869)
    - Regular, Ph-Sch, 2007 (Box 870)
    - Regular, Sel-Ty, 2007 (Box 871)
    - Regular, U-Z, 2007 (Box 872)
    - Withdrawn, A-Z, 2007 (Box 873)
    - Class of 2008, A-Bra (Box 877)
    - Class of 2008, Bre-Cud (Box 878)
    - Class of 2008, Dal-Fon (Box 879)
    - Class of 2008, For-Hir (Box 880)
    - Class of 2008, Hoc-Kle (Box 881)
    - Class of 2008, Kil-Liz (Box 882)
    - Class of 2008, Loi-Murn (Box 883)
    - Class of 2008, Murp-Rob (Box 884)
    - Class of 2008, Roc-Sku (Box 885)
    - Class of 2008, Sla-Wat (Box 886)
    - Class of 2008, Web-Z (Box 887)
    - Class of 2008, withdrawn, A-Z (Box 888)
    - Class of 2009, A-Bur (Box 891)
    - Class of 2009, Bus-Demo (Box 892)
    - Class of 2009, Demp-Gan (Box 893)
    - Class of 2009, Gar-Hom (Box 894)
    - Class of 2009, Hoo-Kri (Box 895)
    - Class of 2009, Kru-Marte (Box 896)
    - Class of 2009, Marti-Pac (Box 897)
    - Class of 2009, Pai-Sab (Box 898)
    - Class of 2009, Sal-Tar (Box 899)
    - Class of 2009, Tat-Z (Box 900)
    - Class of 2009, withdrawn, A-Z (Box 901)
    - Class of 2010, A-Bur (Box 904)
    - Class of 2010, Bur-Do (Box 905)
    - Class of 2010, Dr-Gom (Box 906)
    - Class of 2010, Gon-J (Box 907)
    - Class of 2010, K-Lic (Box 908)
    - Class of 2010, Lic-Mi (Box 909)
    - Class of 2010, Mo-Pin (Box 910)
    - Class of 2010, Pin-Sch (Box 911)
    - Class of 2010, Sch-Tu (Box 912)
    - Class of 2010, Tw-Z (Box 913)
    - Class of 2010, withdrawn, A-Z (Box 914)
    - Class of 2011, A-Bos (Box 915)
    - Class of 2011, Bou-Cro (Box 916)
    - Class of 2011, Cru-Fla (Box 917)
    - Class of 2011, Fli-Hort (Box 918)
    - Class of 2011, Horw-Levi (Box 919)
    - Class of 2011, Levy-Mil (Box 920)
    - Class of 2011, Mink-Pic (Box 921)
    - Class of 2011, Pier-Serg (Box 922)
    - Class of 2011, Sey-Trox (Box 923)
    - Class of 2011, Troy-Z (Box 924)
    - Class of 2011, withdrawn, A-Z (Box 925)
    - Class of 2012, A-Bo (Box 926)
    - Class of 2012, Br-Duo (Box 927)
    - Class of 2012, Dur-Hame (Box 928)
    - Class of 2012, Hamm-Koz (Box 929)
    - Class of 2012, Kro-McD (Box 930)
    - Class of 2012, McF-Q (Box 931)
    - Class of 2012, R-Sl (Box 932)
    - Class of 2012, Sm-Wh (Box 933)
    - Class of 2012, Wie-Z (Box 934)
    - Class of 2012, withdrawn, A-Z (Box 935)
  - Subseries B. Special Students, Programs, And Fellowships, 1912-2016
    - Exchange and Visiting Students, 1969-1972 (Box 664)
    - Exchange and Visiting Students, 1971-1984 (Box 663)
    - Exchange Students, 1989-1990 (Box 687)
    - Fellowships, Hal-Plu, 1912-1966 (Box 38)
    - Fellowships, Lan-Rog, 1912-1966 (Box 27)
    - Fellowships, Pre-Yos, 1912-1966 (Box 37)
    - Fellowships, Ros-Z, 1912-1966 (Box 28)
    - Fellowships, Mixed, circa 1945-1965 (Box 690)
    - Fellowships, B-C, 1948-1960 (Box 13)
    - Fellowships, 1967-1968 (Box 683)
    - Fellowships, 1969-1970 (Box 682)
    - Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 681)
    - Fellowships, 1973-1974 (Box 680)
    - Fellowships, 1974-1975 (Box 679)
    - Fellowships, 1976 (Box 678)
    - Fellowships, 1977 (Box 677)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1978 (Box 676)
    - Fellowships, A-P, 1979 (Box 676)
    - Fellowships, R-Z, 1979 (Box 675)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1980 (Box 675)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1981 (Box 674)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1982 (Box 674)
    - Fellowships, Mixed, 1982 (Box 673)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1983 (Box 673)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1984 (Box 672)
    - Fellowships, A-Z and mixed, 1985 (Box 672)
    - Fellowships, Mixed, 1985 (Box 671)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1986 (Box 671)
    - Fellowships, A-Z, 1987 (Box 670)
    - Fellowships, 1990 (Box 631)
    - Fellowships, 1991 (Box 633)
    - Fellowships, 1992 (Box 634)
    - Fellowships, 1995 (Box 637)
    - Fellowships, 1994-1996 (Box 635)
    - Fellowships, 1998 (Box 632)
    - Fellowships, Rose Applicants, 1971-1976 (Box 669)
    - Fellowships, Rose Applicants, 1976-1978 (Box 667)
    - Fellowships, Maguire Fellowship recipients (half full), 1996-2000 (Box 778)
    - Fellowships, Maguire Fellowship recipients, 2001-2007 (Box 777)
    - Fellowships, Language fellows and interns, [2009?] (Box 902)
    - Graduate students, A-Gl, circa 1920-1950 (Box 689)
    - Graduate students, Go-Mu, circa 1920-1950 (Box 688)
    - Graduate students, circa 1960-1974 (Box 665)
    - Graduate students, 1970-1981 (Box 664)
    - Graduate study, 1969 (Box 903)
    - Junior Year Abroad (JYA), A-Pho, 1991 (Box 686)
    - Junior Year Abroad (JYA), Pil-Z, 1991 (Box 687)
    - Luce Scholars Program for Internships in Asia, 1975-1992 (Box 668)
    - Luce Scholars Program for Internships in Asia, 1993 (Box 629)
    - Pre-Med, 1971-1979 (Box 609)
    - Pre-Med, 1971-1979 (Box 610)
    - Pre-Med, 1972-1982 (Box 874)
    - Pre-Med, 1979-1980 (Box 611)
    - Pre-Med, 1981 (Box 612)
    - Pre-Med, 1981-1983 (Box 618)
    - Pre-Med, 1982-1984 (Box 613)
    - Pre-Med, 1984-1985 (Box 614)
    - Pre-Med, 1986-1987 (Box 615)
    - Pre-Med, 1986-1987 (Box 616)
    - Pre-Med, 1987-1988 (Box 617)
    - Pre-Med, 1988 (Box 619)
    - Pre-Med, 1989 (Box 620)
    - Pre-Med, 1991 (Box 621)
    - Pre-Med, 1992 (Box 622)
    - Pre-Med, 1993 (Box 623)
    - Pre-Med, 1993 (Box 629)
    - Pre-Med, 1994 (Box 624)
    - Pre-Med, 1995 (Box 636)
    - Pre-Med, 1996 (Box 625)
    - Pre-Med, 1997-1998 (Box 626)
    - Pre-Med, A-Q, 1997 (Box 630)
    - Pre-Med, R-Z, 1997 (Box 629)
    - Pre-Med, 1999 (Box 627)
    - Pre-Med, 2000 (Box 628)
    - Pre-Med, 2001 (Box 719)
    - Pre-Med, A-O, 2001 (Box 706)
    - Pre-Med, P-U, 2001 (Box 707)
    - Pre-Med, Cl, Ud, 2001 (Box 629)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2003 (Box 732)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2004 (Box 733)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2005 (Box 734)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2006 (Box 762)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2007 (Box 775)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, A-R, 2008 (Box 807)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, S-W, 2008 (Box 808)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2009 (Box 808)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2010 (Box 809)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2011 (Box 826)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2011 (Box 825)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2012 (Box 875)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, A-B, 2013 (Box 875)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, C-Z, 2013 (Box 876)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2014 (Box 862)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, 2015 (Box 889)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, Ag-Che, 2016 (Box 889)
    - Pre-Med, Accepted, Che-Yu, 2016 (Box 890)
    - Special Students, circa 1968-1974 (Box 662)
    - Special Students, A-G, 1970-1982 (Box 600)
    - Special Students, H-Q, 1970-1982 (Box 601)
    - Special Students, R-Z, 1970-1982 (Box 602)
    - Special Students, 1976-1978 (Box 666)
    - Special Students, A-Lit, 1982-1986 (Box 603)
    - Special Students, Liv-Zyn, 1982-1986 (Box 605)
    - Special Students, Arm-Rob, 1986-1990 (Box 604)
    - Special Students, Ada-Gup, 1986-1994 (Box 606)
    - Special Students, Hac-Rus, 1986-1994 (Box 607)
    - Special Students, Sal-Zwis, 1986-1994 (Box 608)
    - Vassar Fellowships, 1999-2000 (Box 720)
    - Vassar Fellowship applications, 2001 (Box 705)
    - Vassar Fellowships, 2002-2003 (Box 721)
    - Vassar Fellowships, 2004 (Box 722)
    - Vassar Fellowships, Awarded, 2005 (Box 735)
    - Vassar Fellowships, Awarded, 2006 (Box 763)
    - Vassar Fellowships, Awarded, 2007 (Box 764)
    - Vassar Fellowship recipients, 2008 (Box 776)
    - Vassar Fellowship Awarded and declined, 2008-2009 (Box 823)
    - Vassar Fellowship Awarded and declined, 2009-2010 (Box 824)
  - Subseries C. Miscellaneous Files, 1867-2003
    - Admission Material Only, Go-Mo, 1924 (Box 124)
    - Admission Material Only, A-G, 1945 (Box 163)
    - Admission Material Only, Ada-Moer, 1948 (Box 93)
    - Admission Material Only, Mon-Wood, 1948 (Box 92)
    - Admission Material Only, Don-Wood, 1958 (Box 191)
    - Admission Material Only, Ale-Lin, 1960 (Box 201)
    - Admission Material Only, Liv-Yav, 1960 (Box 202)
    - Admission Material Only, Alb-Jos, 1961 (Box 242)
    - Admission Material Only, Kah-Syl, 1961 (Box 243)
    - Admission Material Only, Tap-Zaur, 1961 (Box 522)
    - Averages and rank in classes, 1873-1899 (Box 555)
    - Career development, 1968-1976 (Box 684)
    - Career development, 1973-1976 (Box 685)
    - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 546)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1925 (Box 545)
    - Correspondence, A-C, 1913-1917 (Box 575)
    - Correspondence, withdrawn, 1913-1919 (Box 552)
    - Correspondence, H-M, 1917-1919 (Box 587)
    - Entrance cards, 1967-1968 (Box 657)
    - Exam cards, 1867-1873 (Box 553)
    - Exam cards, 1873-1881 (Box 551)
    - Exam cards, 1881-1889 (Box 559)
    - Exam cards, 1885-1890 (Box 555)
    - Exam cards, 1889-1898 (Box 555)
    - Exam cards, 1894-1896 (Box 548)
    - Exam cards, 1897-1902 (Box 576)
    - Higher Education Opportunity Program (HEOP), 1977-1979 (Box 661)
    - Letters for Entrance, 1905 (Box 597)
    - Letters of Inquiry, 1892-1893 (Box 589)
    - Miscellaneous students, 1969-1984 (Box 810)
    - Student Interview Cards, 1947-1956 (Box 651)
    - Student Interview Cards, A-O, 1958 (Box 652)
    - Student Interview Cards, 1960 (Box 652)
    - Student Interview Cards, 1962 (Box 652)
    - Watson applications, 2003 (Box 704)
    - Withdrawal cards, 1904-1912 (Box 596)
    - Withdrawal cards, 1909-1912 (Box 557)
- Series II. Administrative Records, (79 boxes)
  - Container list unavailable.